sup everyone tablespoon five here with a
very special video today
and boy do I got a doozy for your ass
i just got done watching wonder woman
1984 great movie I highly
recommend it way better than any other
marvel garbage
anyway that's all this is about what
this video is about
is two scenes that I found that has two
sound clips I kill you not
for my videos called two lovers at the
skatepark it's about talking Bobby at
the skatepark going or skating right in
Sonic he goes out in the road and he's
going to get hit by a cow
well anyway this cow honks outside like
saying get out of the road [ __ ]
anyway I think you just need to heal for
yourself listen to this
did you catch that [ __ ] i'll play it
again
[Music]
the only way dc could have gotten this
sound is from me
but I'm not hearing about this so what
the [ __ ] is going on did they steal my
[ __ ]
did they find my bodonic video and they
damn
i like the sound of the cow let's use it
look at what that guy is wearing he's
wearing blue and yellow clothes
locked Bardonic the two lovers that are
featured in my video
and more so than that look at the two
cows that just crash
into each other that's like Bardonic
again Bobby and Sonic
are you kidding me and now let's look at
the next clip
it goes straight from yellow to blue
what is going on here
is this a reference to my videos I can't
believe this [ __ ]
what is going on here what the [ __ ]
damn that's crazy [ __ ]
what the [ __ ] is this oh my God
[Music]